Eginata Kasan

+61 451 059 799 \cdot <u>eginatakasan@gmail.com</u> \cdot <u>eginatakasan.github.io</u> \cdot <u>Linkedin</u> 176 Patrick Street, Hurstville, NSW 2220

ABOUT ME

I'm currently studying Master of Information Technology at UTS while working part-time as a software developer in Sydney. I work for QSStudio for over a year and was a UX Engineer for Nomura Research Institute Indonesia for over 2 years. A firm believer in the spirit of teamwork, I enjoy collaborating with others to drive towards meaningful objectives.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer (Part-Time)

May 2024 - Now

QSStudio, Sydney, Australia

- Worked on both website and mobile app development for varying projects
- Mobile app development with React Native
- Front-end web development with React-Typescript, Vite and Back-end development with Node, Supabase, MongoDB, and AWS CDK
- In-between tasks such as: analytics setup with Mixpanel and Firebase, workflow automation with n8n, email/notification integrations with
- Collaborated with a small team of a Software Engineer and Al Engineers

UX Engineer

October 2021 - January 2024

Nomura Research Institute Indonesia, Jakarta, Indonesia

- Front-end development with emphasis on UI precision & UX improvement
- Mobile app developments with React Native and responsive/fluid website development with React, Vue, and pure HTML/CSS/JS
- Developed UI library for company with Storybook
- High attention to micro-interactions
- Worked on multiple projects from national & international clients
- Collaborated with different teams, consisting of project owners, managers and co-workers from Indonesia and Japan

Games Programmer Intern

June 2019 - August 2019

Agate Games Studio, Bandung, Indonesia

- Worked with a team of four to develop company framework using Unity (C#) and Google Firebase
- Was awarded a Golden Ticket distinction for a job well done

EDUCATION

Master of Information Technology

February 2024 - Current

University of Technology Sydney (UTS)

- Awardee of UTS Postgraduate Academic Excellence International Scholarship
- Three-time nominee for UTS Tech Fest for: Software Engineering, Prototyping, and Games Development

Bachelor of Computer Science

July 2017 - July 2021

Bandung Institute of Technology

- Wrote dissertation on metrics to quantify User Experience in B2C e-commerce
- Head of Algorithm for Fire Extinguisher Robot Team (2018)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frameworks

Web Development: React, Vue.js, Node, Vite, Redux, AWS CDK, Firebase, Tailwind, CSS, Sass, n8n

App Development: React Native, Android Studio, Unity, Nativewind

Programming Languages

Javascript/Typescript, HTML/CSS, Java, Python, C#, C++, PHP

RELEVANT PROJECTS

Al Powered Beauty Assistant Mobile App

Mobile & Backend Development - React Native, AWS CDK, Typescript, Supabase

- A currently-published app that uses AI to recommend or give advice on beauty products according to the user's skin type
- Frontend development of the app includes building features such as identifying scanned objects (with Google MLKit and VisionCamera), recording user answers for tailored recommendations and managing subscription and credits system. App is built on React Native / Typescript
- Backend development uses lambda server deployed using AWS CDK and Supabase (Postgres) database

Petrol Finder & Price Tracker Mobile App

Mobile & Backend Development - React Native, Typescript, Supabase, MongoDB

- The app finds nearest petrol station and displays prices, save user preferences and notifies on increase/decrease of these prices
- Migrated the app from MongoDB to Supabase as MongoDB will reach Data API and HTTPS Endpoints end-of-life

Point of Sales Web App for Startup

Frontend Development - ReactJS, Redux and Typescript

- Two web applications designed for restaurant management with printable QR, menus/table management and subscription admin
- Features include restaurant menu management, restaurant table management, admin panel, basic authentication, form validation and QR generation

Document Management Website

Frontend Development - ReactJS, Redux and Typescript

- · Created a website for storing and sharing documents across users
- · Designed User Interface and UI kit for the website

Food Stock Management Mobile App

Frontend Development - React Native, Redux, Typescript

- A mobile app for convenience store managers to reduce fried food waste by managing food quantities and creation/disposal schedule
- Confronted UI challenge of complicated nested scroll tables and huge table inside modals
- Managed to improve overall application performance

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Women in Engineering and IT Community UTS Tech Society

REFERENCES

Available upon request

CERTIFICATIONS

Google's Foundation of UX Design

June 2023

Coursera

<u>Dynamic User Experience: Dynamic and Usability</u>

January 2023

Interaction Design Foundation

<u>Design for the 21th Century with Don Norman</u>

January 2023

Interaction Design Foundation

Mobile UX Design August 2022

Interaction Design Foundation